[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 9, "question": "Eva, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["Eva", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 10, "answer": "I'm good.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 11, "question": "How are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 12, "answer": "Lovely to have you in my studio.", "answer_tokens": ["Lovely", "to", "have", "you", "in", "my", "studio", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 35, "question": "What do you mean?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "mean", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 36, "answer": "Occupation.", "answer_tokens": ["Occupation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "What do you call yourself?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "call", "yourself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "Actor is on there.", "answer_tokens": ["Actor", "is", "on", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 51, "question": "That excites me?", "question_tokens": ["That", "excites", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 52, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 58, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 59, "answer": "I mean like when you're older you have a better appreciation for history or for knowledge.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", "like", "when", "you", "'re", "older", "you", "have", "a", "better", "appreciation", "for", "history", "or", "for", "knowledge", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 62, "question": "What are you -- what are you actually studying?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "--", "what", "are", "you", "actually", "studying", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 63, "answer": "Chicano studies and political science.", "answer_tokens": ["Chicano", "studies", "and", "political", "science", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 64, "question": "ORGAN: What is Chicano studies?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "What", "is", "Chicano", "studies", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 65, "answer": "Chicano studies is the study mostly of the Mexican- American movement that has happened in the United States, and the history of Mexican-Americans.", "answer_tokens": ["Chicano", "studies", "is", "the", "study", "mostly", "of", "the", "Mexican-", "American", "movement", "that", "has", "happened", "in", "the", "United", "States", ",", "and", "the", "history", "of", "Mexican-Americans", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 72, "question": "Can I?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "I", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 73, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 74, "question": "You can be an honorary Chicano?", "question_tokens": ["You", "can", "be", "an", "honorary", "Chicano", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 75, "answer": "You can be an honorary Chicano.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "can", "be", "an", "honorary", "Chicano", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 76, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 77, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 78, "question": "What do I have to do?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "I", "have", "to", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 79, "answer": "Well, you have to help us in the fight for social justice and believe in equality for everyone.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "have", "to", "help", "us", "in", "the", "fight", "for", "social", "justice", "and", "believe", "in", "equality", "for", "everyone", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 81, "question": "How important are your roots to you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "important", "are", "your", "roots", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 82, "answer": "Pretty important.", "answer_tokens": ["Pretty", "important", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 93, "question": "You had to learn Spanish?", "question_tokens": ["You", "had", "to", "learn", "Spanish", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 94, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 102, "question": "Do you speak French?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "speak", "French", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 103, "answer": "I speak a bit of French.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "speak", "a", "bit", "of", "French", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "Immigration?", "question_tokens": ["Immigration", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "When I came here, I couldn't believe the hot issue it really is.", "answer_tokens": ["When", "I", "came", "here", ",", "I", "could", "n't", "believe", "the", "hot", "issue", "it", "really", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 125, "question": "How would you fix things?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "fix", "things", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 126, "answer": "Well, that's a loaded question.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "a", "loaded", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 143, "question": "Do you think he has lived up to expectations?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "he", "has", "lived", "up", "to", "expectations", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "TO", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 144, "answer": "I think he had a lot on his plate.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "had", "a", "lot", "on", "his", "plate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", ":", "RB", "PRP", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 173, "question": "It's heartbreaking to see kids having to do this in modern ages, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "heartbreaking", "to", "see", "kids", "having", "to", "do", "this", "in", "modern", "ages", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 174, "answer": "The great thing about this documentary is that -- actually we produced it so it can be used as a political tool to change the way agricultural workers are treated in the United States.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "great", "thing", "about", "this", "documentary", "is", "that", "--", "actually", "we", "produced", "it", "so", "it", "can", "be", "used", "as", "a", "political", "tool", "to", "change", "the", "way", "agricultural", "workers", "are", "treated", "in", "the", "United", "States", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 188, "question": "ORGAN: You're quite an activist, aren't you?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "You", "'re", "quite", "an", "activist", ",", "are", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 189, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 198, "question": "Yes?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 199, "answer": "I shouldn't be, but I am.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "should", "n't", "be", ",", "but", "I", "am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 239, "question": "How do you deal with that as someone who's got in your own family?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "deal", "with", "that", "as", "someone", "who", "'s", "got", "in", "your", "own", "family", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 240, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 244, "question": "How is she doing?", "question_tokens": ["How", "is", "she", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 245, "answer": "She's doing amazing.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "'s", "doing", "amazing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 277, "question": "To have somebody in your life who none of that means anything to at all and who's not impressed by any of that because why would she be?", "question_tokens": ["To", "have", "somebody", "in", "your", "life", "who", "none", "of", "that", "means", "anything", "to", "at", "all", "and", "who", "'s", "not", "impressed", "by", "any", "of", "that", "because", "why", "would", "she", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "NN", "TO", "IN", "DT", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "IN", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 278, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 279, "question": "It makes it very natural for you, doesn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "makes", "it", "very", "natural", "for", "you", ",", "does", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 280, "answer": "She's very grounding.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "'s", "very", "grounding", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 299, "question": "Don't you find that a bit unsettling when you go home?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "n't", "you", "find", "that", "a", "bit", "unsettling", "when", "you", "go", "home", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 300, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 302, "question": "No entourage?", "question_tokens": ["No", "entourage", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 317, "question": "What's the matter with you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "matter", "with", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 318, "answer": "I'm really not a complainer.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "really", "not", "a", "complainer", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 322, "question": "Do we say slouch, lay back, think of England?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "we", "say", "slouch", ",", "lay", "back", ",", "think", "of", "England", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", ",", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "I'm going to go sit in your lap.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "going", "to", "go", "sit", "in", "your", "lap", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["England"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 325, "question": "Why do you think I put you in an uncomfortable chair?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "think", "I", "put", "you", "in", "an", "uncomfortable", "chair", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 326, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 331, "question": "Aren't you?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Demi Moore", "Ashton"]}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "VBD", ",", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 360, "question": "What's the attraction of Twitter?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "attraction", "of", "Twitter", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 361, "answer": "You know it's funny because Demi Moore and Ashton were, like, you know, the really pioneers of getting everybody on Twitter.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", "it", "'s", "funny", "because", "Demi", "Moore", "and", "Ashton", "were", ",", "like", ",", "you", "know", ",", "the", "really", "pioneers", "of", "getting", "everybody", "on", "Twitter", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "Are you a drunk tweeter?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "a", "drunk", "tweeter", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "No, not drunk tweeting.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "drunk", "tweeting", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 387, "question": "It's more to do with putting stuff out there where you -- why did I do that?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "more", "to", "do", "with", "putting", "stuff", "out", "there", "where", "you", "--", "why", "did", "I", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "TO", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "EX", "WRB", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 388, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 396, "question": "Like if you choose to make your life so private?", "question_tokens": ["Like", "if", "you", "choose", "to", "make", "your", "life", "so", "private", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 397, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 406, "question": "Because it's so easy now to become a celebrity?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "it", "'s", "so", "easy", "now", "to", "become", "a", "celebrity", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 407, "answer": "No, because I mean -- really I don't really care.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "because", "I", "mean", "--", "really", "I", "do", "n't", "really", "care", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 417, "question": "You're look like a mini Oprah, aren't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "look", "like", "a", "mini", "Oprah", ",", "are", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Oprah"]}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "What's the Eva Longoria brand?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "Eva", "Longoria", "brand", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "Well, I think similar to Oprah.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "similar", "to", "Oprah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Eva Longoria"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "Are you tough enough to be a mogul, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "tough", "enough", "to", "be", "a", "mogul", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 451, "question": "Are you not to be messed with?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "not", "to", "be", "messed", "with", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "I am not to be messed with.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "not", "to", "be", "messed", "with", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 464, "question": "I mean seriously, could you ever go out with a man with a soft handshake?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "seriously", ",", "could", "you", "ever", "go", "out", "with", "a", "man", "with", "a", "soft", "handshake", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 465, "answer": "Never.", "answer_tokens": ["Never", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 473, "question": "Who?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 474, "answer": "I'm not going to name them now.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "going", "to", "name", "them", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 481, "question": "Who taught you direct eye contact and firm handshake?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "taught", "you", "direct", "eye", "contact", "and", "firm", "handshake", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": "Probably my family.", "answer_tokens": ["Probably", "my", "family", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 485, "question": "They're all strong women, aren't they?", "question_tokens": ["They", "'re", "all", "strong", "women", ",", "are", "n't", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 486, "answer": "And they're all strong.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "they", "'re", "all", "strong", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "What do they make -- what do they make of what's happened to you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "they", "make", "--", "what", "do", "they", "make", "of", "what", "'s", "happened", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "They're proud.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "'re", "proud", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 499, "question": "Are they -- do they quite believe it?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "they", "--", "do", "they", "quite", "believe", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 500, "answer": "Well, I was always different.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "was", "always", "different", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "Do I like being famous?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "I", "like", "being", "famous", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 521, "question": "Or does it make no difference?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "does", "it", "make", "no", "difference", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 522, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 530, "question": "Did you imagine you would be married for life?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "imagine", "you", "would", "be", "married", "for", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 531, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 535, "question": "But did you really believe this was the guy, this was the one for you for life?", "question_tokens": ["But", "did", "you", "really", "believe", "this", "was", "the", "guy", ",", "this", "was", "the", "one", "for", "you", "for", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "DT", "VBD", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 553, "question": "What?", "question_tokens": ["What", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 554, "answer": "It all came out.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "all", "came", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "The marriage?", "question_tokens": ["The", "marriage", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 586, "question": "Do you feel humiliated?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "humiliated", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 587, "answer": "A bit, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "bit", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 592, "question": "What more could a guy want, frankly?", "question_tokens": ["What", "more", "could", "a", "guy", "want", ",", "frankly", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "JJR", "MD", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 593, "answer": "Well, you know, like I said, we just -- you want different things.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "like", "I", "said", ",", "we", "just", "--", "you", "want", "different", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 613, "question": "Is there any way back as far as you're concerned, if a man behaves that way towards you?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "any", "way", "back", "as", "far", "as", "you", "'re", "concerned", ",", "if", "a", "man", "behaves", "that", "way", "towards", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 614, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Senate", "House"], "PERSON": ["Harry Reid", "John Boehner"]}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 628, "question": "What are you hearing?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "hearing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 629, "answer": "I just got a joint statement, I should tell you, from the Senate Majority Leader Harry Reid and House Speaker John Boehner.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "just", "got", "a", "joint", "statement", ",", "I", "should", "tell", "you", ",", "from", "the", "Senate", "Majority", "Leader", "Harry", "Reid", "and", "House", "Speaker", "John", "Boehner", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 639, "question": "But this is more what about social issues, about these riders that the Republicans are asking for?", "question_tokens": ["But", "this", "is", "more", "what", "about", "social", "issues", ",", "about", "these", "riders", "that", "the", "Republicans", "are", "asking", "for", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "RBR", "WP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "DT", "NNPS", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 640, "answer": "Social and economic issues.", "answer_tokens": ["Social", "and", "economic", "issues", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 643, "question": "What issues in particular?", "question_tokens": ["What", "issues", "in", "particular", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 644, "answer": "Let's just give you the two biggies.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "'s", "just", "give", "you", "the", "two", "biggies", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WDT", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "CC", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 695, "question": "What are the issues that they're most apart on?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "the", "issues", "that", "they", "'re", "most", "apart", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 696, "answer": "We started talking about some of the policy issues that aren't so much related to the big fight, which of course is spending and spending cuts.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "started", "talking", "about", "some", "of", "the", "policy", "issues", "that", "are", "n't", "so", "much", "related", "to", "the", "big", "fight", ",", "which", "of", "course", "is", "spending", "and", "spending", "cuts", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 735, "question": "Why should I get excited by your cookbook?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "should", "I", "get", "excited", "by", "your", "cookbook", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 736, "answer": "I love to cook.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "love", "to", "cook", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 745, "question": "Yes, oh, it's called guac, is it?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "oh", ",", "it", "'s", "called", "guac", ",", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 746, "answer": "Well, guacamole.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "guacamole", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 751, "question": "Now are these your little signature things?", "question_tokens": ["Now", "are", "these", "your", "little", "signature", "things", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "DT", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 752, "answer": "These are my signature things.", "answer_tokens": ["These", "are", "my", "signature", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 771, "question": "Now the interview starts, huh?", "question_tokens": ["Now", "the", "interview", "starts", ",", "huh", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 772, "answer": "I love margaritas.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "love", "margaritas", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 775, "question": "But this is all quite simple food, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["But", "this", "is", "all", "quite", "simple", "food", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 776, "answer": "It's all very simple and, you know, I'm not a chef.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "all", "very", "simple", "and", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "a", "chef", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 785, "question": "Do you think there's someone watching this who can't cook, like me, if they read this book?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "there", "'s", "someone", "watching", "this", "who", "ca", "n't", "cook", ",", "like", "me", ",", "if", "they", "read", "this", "book", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "WP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 786, "answer": "If you can read, you can cook.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "you", "can", "read", ",", "you", "can", "cook", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 815, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 816, "answer": "You know, the people you reach.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "the", "people", "you", "reach", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 822, "question": "Oh, God, what are you going to say?", "question_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "God", ",", "what", "are", "you", "going", "to", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 823, "answer": "Sex.", "answer_tokens": ["Sex", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 836, "question": "Did she tell you that?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "she", "tell", "you", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 837, "answer": "She told me that.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "told", "me", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 838, "question": "On air?", "question_tokens": ["On", "air", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 839, "answer": "No, it wasn't on air, no.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "it", "was", "n't", "on", "air", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gwyn"]}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 845, "question": "None?", "question_tokens": ["None", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 846, "answer": "ONGORIA: Good for Gwyn.", "answer_tokens": ["ONGORIA", ":", "Good", "for", "Gwyn", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 852, "question": "Is that true?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 853, "answer": "I am.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 860, "question": "When you see the Oscars on TV, do you think -- do you start practicing the speech that may never happen?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "see", "the", "Oscars", "on", "TV", ",", "do", "you", "think", "--", "do", "you", "start", "practicing", "the", "speech", "that", "may", "never", "happen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ":", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 861, "answer": "No, I don't.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 867, "question": "Do you like politics?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "like", "politics", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 868, "answer": "I actually love --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "actually", "love", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 883, "question": "Can you imagine?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "imagine", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 884, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 887, "question": "What about Oprah-Eva ticket?", "question_tokens": ["What", "about", "Oprah-Eva", "ticket", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 888, "answer": "I know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 893, "question": "What's been the moment you'd relive tomorrow if you had the chance?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "been", "the", "moment", "you", "'d", "relive", "tomorrow", "if", "you", "had", "the", "chance", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 894, "answer": "You know, people ask me this all the time.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "people", "ask", "me", "this", "all", "the", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Andy Garcia"]}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", ":", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "``", "NNP", "''", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 912, "question": "Any movies?", "question_tokens": ["Any", "movies", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 913, "answer": "Well, yes, I just did -- finished a film called \"Cristiada\" with Andy Garcia.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "yes", ",", "I", "just", "did", "--", "finished", "a", "film", "called", "``", "Cristiada", "''", "with", "Andy", "Garcia", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["fall"]}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 918, "question": "When's it out?", "question_tokens": ["When", "'s", "it", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 919, "answer": "In the fall.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "the", "fall", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110407pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 932, "question": "Let's finish our margaritas, shall we?", "question_tokens": ["Let", "'s", "finish", "our", "margaritas", ",", "shall", "we", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "JJ", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 933, "answer": "OK, we shall.", "answer_tokens": ["OK", ",", "we", "shall", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]